A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Office of Communications, Photographic Collection, No. 1300-1356 FA662
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Office of Communications, Photographic Collection, No. 1300-1356
1999-2000
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA662
1.2 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access note
Material more than ten years old is open for scholarly research.
Select individual files are restricted, as noted. Permission to access these files must be obtained from the Ford Foundation before scholarly access is permitted.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be restricted from scholarly research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment. Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be restricted from scholarly research at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/RAC Head of Reference.
Ford Foundation
- 1300 Devolution Initiative (PSJ), Ford Foundation Conference, Birmingham AL. (1/2), Nov 17-19, 1999 (Box 1)
- 1300 Devolution Initiative (PSJ), Ford Foundation Conference, Birmingham AL. (2/2), Nov 17-19, 1999 (Box 1)
- 1302 Peru Story -- Flora Tristan, DEMUS and CLADEM (ASSETS/HDRH)., Winter 2000 (Box 1)
- 1303 AR99 South Africa -- Namibia, University of Namibia, North Campus (PSJ/Civil Society)., 1999 (Box 1)
- 1304A India Office, Dakshinachitra, Tamil Nadu (EMAC/Arts and Culture), 1999 (Box 1)
- 1304B India Office, Vidhayak Sansad (PSJ/Social Justice), 1999 (Box 1)
- 1304C India Office, Disha, Ahmedabad (PSJ/Human Rights), 1999 (Box 1)
- 1304D India Office, ATI, Enterprise Works Worldwide (ASSETS/Community and Land Management), 1999 (Box 1)
- 1304E India Office, Viksat, Gujarat (ASSETS/Community Water Resources), 1999 (Box 1)
- 1304F India Office, Vikalp, Gujarat (ASSETS/Reproductive Health), 1999 (Box 1)
- 1304G Annual Report, India/Nepal, WICOM (ASSETS/HDRH), 1999 (Box 1)
- 1305 Annual Report -- Santiago Office -- CONSORTIUM (ASSETS/Community Development), 1999 (Box 1)
- 1307 Program Associates -- The Ford Foundation, Feb 2, 2000 (Box 1)
- 1308 Devolution Initiative (PSJ/GCS), Spring 2000 (Box 1)
- 1309 Spring Report -- Advanced Placement Story -- Darren Dix at Inglewood High (EMAC/EKR), Spring 2000 (Box 1)
- 1310 Neighborhood Reinvestment Corp. (ASSETS), Spring 2000 (Box 1)
- 1311 Groundbreaking for James F. Oyster Bilingual School in Washington DC (EMAC), Dec 10, 1999 (Box 1)
- 1312 New Directions/New Donors -- Ford Foundation Arts Initiative, May 10, 2000 (Box 1)
- 1313 National Security Archives, George Washington University, Portrait of Tom Blanton, Washington DC (PSJ/HRIC) (Box 1)
- 1315 Human Serve -- Cloward & Piven (PSJ/GCS), n.d. (Box 1)
- 1316 Equality Now -- Women Can't Wait -- Sarah Jones performs at the Ford Foundation, Jun 8, 2000 (Box 1)
- 1317 Native American Trust Fund -- Elouise Cobell -- Blackfeet Development Fund -- Dennis Gingold in Washington DC, Jul 26, 2000 (Box 1)
- 1318 Caryn McTighe Musil -- Campus Diversity -- AAC&U (EMAC/EKR), Fall 2000 (Box 1)
- 1322 Rebecca Johnson/Acronym Institute -- Nuclear Nonproliferation Story (PSJ/HRIC), Fall 2000 (Box 1)
- 1323 President of Vietnam, Tran Duc Luong at the Ford Foundation, Sep 8, 2000 (Box 1)
- 1324 Program Associates, 2000-2002 (Box 1)
- 1325 Predatory Lending Practices -- Philadelphia Neighborhoods (Box 1)
- 1326 Annual Report -- Piton Foundation (ASSETS/Community Development), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1327 Annual Report -- Santa Ana Unified School District (EMAC/Education Reform), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1328 Annual Report -- Liberty Hill Foundation (PSJ/Civil Society), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1329 Annual Report -- Sara Horowitz/Working Today (ASSETS/Workforce Development), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1330 Annual Report -- Center for Economic and Social Rights (PSJ/Human Rights), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1331 Annual Report -- Columbia University/Islamic Mapping Project (EMAC/RSC), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1332 Annual Report -- Project GRAD/Newark (EMAC/Education Reform), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1333 -- Annual Report -- Collins Center for Public Policy (ASSETS/Community Development), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1334 -- Annual Report -- Welfare Law Center (ASSETS/CYF), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1335 -- Annual Report -- Public Education Network (EMAC/Education Reform), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1336 Annual Report -- Faraja Trust Fund -- Tanzania (ASSETS/SRH), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1337 Annual Report -- Kibale Forest Coffe Project -- Uganda (ASSETS/Environment and Development), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1338 Annual Report -- Makerere University Refugee Law Project -- Kenya (PSJ/Human Rights), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1339 Annual Report -- Kituo Cha Katiba -- East Africa Centre for Constitutional Development -- Kenya (PSJ/Governance), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1340 Annual Report -- Kuona Trust -- Kenya (EMAC/Arts and Culture), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1341 Annual Report -- Institute of Politics and Governance (PSJ/Governance), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1342 Annual Report -- Community of Learners Foundation (EMAC/Education Reform), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1343 Annual Report -- Self Sufficiency Standard (ASSETS/Workforce Development), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1346 Annual Report -- Institute of World Economics and Politics/CASS -- China (PSJ/International Cooperation), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1347 Annual Report -- Community College Project/US-China Education Foundation -- China -- (EMAC/Education Reform), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1348 Annual Report -- Womens Studies in China -- China (EMAC/HES), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1349 Annual Report -- Development Exchange Centre -- Nigeria (ASSETS/DFES), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1350 Annual Report -- African Radio Drama Association -- Nigeria (EMAC/Media), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1351 Annual Report -- Lagos State Government--Directorate for Citizens' Rights (Nigeria), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1352 Annual Report -- AFL-CIO Working for America (ASSETS/Workforce Development), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1353 Annual Report -- Birzeit University -- Egypt (ASSETS/SRH), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1354 Annual Report -- the Aga Khan Trust for Culture -- Egypt (ASSETS/Community Development), 2000 (Box 1)
- 1356 Annual Report -- Al Quds University -- Palestine (PSJ/International Cooperation), 2000 (Box 1)